in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can fill between paths using
您可以使用以下命令在路径之间填充
inkscape and to show you what I mean I
Inkscape，并向你展示我的意思
have this series of individual lines on
将这一系列单独的行放在
my screen here if I grab my nodes tool
我的屏幕在这里，如果我抓住我的节点工具
you can see these are just independent
你可以看到这些都是独立的
paths
路径
and if I select all of these paths and
如果我选择所有这些路径并
try to apply a fill color you can see
试着应用你能看到的填充颜色
that nothing happens there because these
那里什么都不会发生因为这些
shapes between these paths aren't
这些路径之间的形状不是
actually shapes this is just empty space
实际上这只是一片空旷的空间
that takes on the appearance of a shape
它呈现出一个形状的外观
so if I want to fill in these spaces we
所以如果我想填上这些空白处
have to use a different approach
必须使用一种不同的方法
so there's actually several different
所以实际上有几种不同的
ways that you can do this and the method
可以做到这一点的方法和方法
that you should use depends on which
您应该使用哪一种取决于
result you're going for so let's have a
你想要的结果，所以让我们有一个
closer look if I select all of these
如果我选择所有这些选项，请仔细查看
shapes right here I can go to path and
就在这里，我可以转到Path和
choose fracture
选择断开
and what happens is it creates
所发生的是它创造了
independent shapes out of all of those
所有这些形状都是独立的
empty spaces there and now you can just
那里空荡荡的，现在你可以
select them and go and change their
选择它们，然后转到并更改其
colors as you'd like
你喜欢的颜色
another way that you can do this is by
您可以使用的另一种方法是
using the shape Builder tool if I select
使用形状构建器工具(如果我选择
all of these shapes and go into the
所有这些形状并进入
shape Builder tool I can get the same
形状构建器工具我可以得到相同的
result as fracture the only difference
结果作为骨折，唯一的区别是
now is that I can make I can combine
现在是我可以让我可以结合
some of these shapes together so I can
其中的一些形状放在一起，这样我就可以
create this cube-like effect like that
像这样创建这个立方体般的效果
now the problem with using this approach
现在使用这种方法的问题是
is that it doesn't just fill in those
它不只是填入那些
empty spaces it also gets rid of the uh
空白处也去掉了这个
the lines that I had there so if you
我在那里的台词，所以如果你
want to do this in such a way that you
想要以这样一种方式来做这件事
can fill between these paths and still
可以填充在这些路径之间，并且仍然
preserve these paths one way to do that
保留这些路径是实现这一点的一种方法
would be to use the paint bucket tool so
就是使用油漆桶工具
I'm going to come over here and grab the
我要到这里来拿起
paint bucket tool in the in the toolbar
工具栏中的中的画桶工具
you can also access it by pressing the
您也可以通过按
letter U on your keyboard
键盘上的字母U
and we'll come up here to the tool
我们会来到这个工具的前面
settings menu and make sure you have the
设置菜单，并确保您有
fill by set to visible colors make sure
填充方式设置为可见颜色可确保
your threshold is set to 50. we'll start
您的阈值设置为50。我们要开始了
out at 50 and if we need to adjust it
如果我们需要调整它的话
we'll increase or decrease it grow and
我们会增加或减少它的增长和
Shrink make sure you have that set to
收缩确保已将其设置为
zero and close gaps set to none
将零间隙和闭合间隙设置为无
now you can choose a fill color that
现在您可以选择一种填充颜色
you'd like to use it's indicated up here
你想用上面标明的
in the top right corner you can see as
在右上角，您可以看到
of right now green is my fill color if I
现在绿色是我的填充色，如果我
want to change my fill color I could
想要更改我的填充颜色我可以
just come down here to the color bar and
只要下来这里的颜色吧和
pick one of these other colors
从这些其他颜色中挑选一种
and now if I click on one of these empty
现在如果我点击其中一个空的
spaces it fills in that empty space with
它用来填充空格的空格
the new Vector shape
新的矢量形状
now if I zoom in on this you can see
现在，如果我放大这个，你可以看到
where this effect is not perfect you can
在这种效果不完美的地方，你可以
see there are a little bit of gaps in
你看，这里有一点空隙
there it didn't exactly fill it in
在那里，它并没有准确地填写它
precisely so let me undo that by
正是如此，让我通过以下方式撤销它
pressing Ctrl Z or command Z if you're
如果是，请按Ctrl Z或Command Z
on Mac and I'm going to come up here to
在Mac上，我要来这里
the tool settings what we can choose to
该工具设置了我们可以选择的内容
do is we can choose to grow or Shrink
我们可以选择增长或缩小
The Fill using this setting right here
在此处使用此设置的填充
so if I increase this to 0.7
所以如果我把它增加到0.7
and try that again
然后再试一次
you can see it fills it in better as you
你可以看到它填充得更好，因为你
can see there but the problem now is
我看得出来，但现在的问题是
that it's overlapping some of the path
它重叠了一些小路
here so what you'll want to do is grab
在这里，你要做的是抓起
your select tool and then just lower
你的选择工具，然后放低
this beneath the pads like that and now
像那样的垫子下面，现在
you can grab the paint bucket tool again
您可以再次抓起画桶工具
and proceed to fill in the other colors
然后继续填写其他颜色
now if you want to change colors while
现在，如果您想在更改颜色时
you're filling them in make sure to
你要把它们填进去，确保
press the Escape key so you can deselect
按Esc键，这样可以取消选择
whatever object you currently have
您当前拥有的任何对象
selected and then you can choose your
选中，然后您可以选择您的
next color like that
下一种颜色是那样的
and then press Escape when you want to
然后在需要时按Escape键
choose another color again
再次选择另一种颜色
and then you could fill it like that
然后你就可以像这样填满它
okay so now what I'm going to do is I'm
好的，所以现在我要做的是
going to take all of my shapes here I'm
我要在这里展现我所有的造型
going to select them all
我要把它们都选出来
and I'm going to send them all to the
我要把他们都送到
back so that we can see the paths on top
后退，这样我们就可以看到上面的小路了
of them
其中之一
and you can see again this approach is
您可以再次看到，这种方法是
not perfect we have these gaps in here
并不完美，我们这里有这些空隙
despite using despite changing those
尽管使用，尽管改变了这些
settings so I'm going to grab my nodes
设置，所以我要获取节点
tool and I'm going to take these nodes
工具，我将使用这些节点
and move them and adjust them so that
并移动和调整它们，以便
everything here is filled in accurately
这里的所有东西都填得很准确
and there we go foreign
在那里我们走出国门
so one thing to keep in mind when using
所以在使用时要记住一件事
the paint bucket tool is if I fill in
油漆桶工具是如果我填上
this shape right here I have a shape but
这个形状在这里我有一个形状，但是
if I try doing that over here it doesn't
如果我在这里试一试，它不会
work and the reason why is because if I
工作和原因是因为如果我
zoom in you can see there is a gap
放大你可以看到有一个缺口
between these paths here meaning this is
在这些路径之间，这意味着这是
all open space the paint bucket tool
所有开放空间油漆桶工具
mostly only works on closed spaces there
大多只在那里的封闭空间工作
are no gaps here so it worked over here
这里没有缝隙，所以它可以在这里工作
there is a setting that you can use to
有一个设置可以用来
change this though so if I come up here
改变这一点，这样如果我来到这里
to the tool settings where it says close
添加到工具设置，其中显示为关闭
gaps I can start off with small and see
我可以从很小的差距开始，然后看到
if that works so I'll set it to small
如果可以的话，我会把它设置成小的。
and click on it
然后点击它
okay so this is this must be larger than
好的，这就是这一定比
what inkscapes considers to be a small
墨迹被认为是一个小的
Gap so I'm going to try medium now
所以我现在要试一试中号的
because that didn't work so let's try
因为那不管用，所以让我们试一试
medium
5~6成熟
there we go
好了，我们走吧
and this time it works so based on the
这一次，它的工作原理是基于
size of the of the gaps between your
您之间的间隙的大小
paths go ahead and cycle through those
小路继续前行，穿过那些
options there to see if one of those
那里的选项，看看其中一个
will work if you're encountering that
如果您遇到这种情况，将会起作用
problem
问题
so all of the methods that we've gone
所以我们所采用的所有方法
over at this point have been imperfect
在这一点上一直是不完美的
in some way let's go over a workflow
在某种程度上，让我们回顾一下工作流程
that is perfect what I'm going to do is
太棒了，我接下来要做的是
I'm going to select my paths here and
我要在这里选择我的道路
I'm going to combine them together by
我将通过以下方式将它们结合起来
going to path and selecting combine
转到路径并选择组合
now I'm going to duplicate that I'm
现在我要重复一遍，我是
going to right click it and go to
右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate
复本
and now I'm going to apply the fracture
现在我要把骨折
to this duplicated path here so I'll go
到这条重复的小路，所以我要走了
to path and select fracture
要创建路径并选择断开
and now I can change the colors of my
现在我可以改变我的颜色
shapes and I could remove The Stroke by
形状和我可以移除笔划
holding shift and clicking on this red X
按住Shift键并单击此红色X
over here and now I can send them to the
在这里，现在我可以把他们送到
back and this workflow right here gives
回到这里，这个工作流程给出了
you the best result the only problem
你是最好的结果，唯一的问题
with this method here is that now you
用这种方法，你现在是不是
have to go and change all of these
我得去改变这一切
colors individually if you need the
如果需要，请单独使用颜色
colors to be different
颜色要有所不同
so that is how you can go about filling
所以这就是你如何去填充
between paths using inkscape if you
在路径之间使用Inkscape，如果您
found this lesson useful then consider
觉得这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and I explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示了它们的工作方式
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这段视频中所做的
even have a private Community where you
甚至拥有一个私人社区，在那里你可以
can ask questions and get help from me
可以问我问题并得到我的帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何你想要的时间，最好的是有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
你只需支付月费就可以了
17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
17一次，你就会被判终身监禁
have some information about that down
我有一些关于这方面的信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想要将其查看为
always thanks for watching foreign
一直感谢收看外国语节目